Contact

codegenerator1994@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/codegenerator19940131 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Artificial intelligence

HTML / CSS / JavaScript

React / Redux / Next

Material UI / Tailwind CSS

Python / Django

Angular / Angular JS

Node / Express

Vue / PHP / Laravel

AWS / Azure / Docker

Git / GitHub / GitLab / Bitbucket

Team Leadership

Team Management

Agile Methodologies

Daily Report

Daily Scrum

Chiyo Wisozk

Proven and experienced Full-Stack Engineer

Waterloo, Ontario N2L 3G1, Canada

Summary

Senior Full Stack Engineer with 8+ years of experience designing, developing, maintaining web & mobile services and apps. Excellent ability to meet deadlines and work as part of a team to deliver great work. High proficiency in object-oriented methodologies, data structures, and algorithms, as well as quality coding and excellent debugging skills. Since I'm a cool-hearted person, so usually see every difficulty with a positive side and keep myself always smiling which makes me stronger even. Proven track record in optimizing application performance, reducing bugs, and improving overall code quality, resulting in increased user engagement and revenue growth.

Experience

Costo Al

Senior Frontend & DevOps Engineer January 2024 - May 2024 (5 months)

- Managed and developed whole frontend side using React/Redux.
- Worked with COO and CEO directly to get requirements to implement financial logics.
- Worked as DevOps Engineer to host React frontend and Django backend using AWS and GoDaddy.
- Managed source using Git/GitHub.
- Fixed and maintenance backend Structure, database Model and logic.

DazzleLabs

Principal Skilled Full Stack Engineer & Team leader September 2022 - December 2023 (1 years 4 months)

- ✓ Supervised a team of 7 developers to develop the ecommerce websites to increase 20% revenue using Python, Django and React.
- ✓ Boosted system performance by optimizing database queries and reducing server response time. reducing bounce rate by 5.5%.
- ✓ Developed 2 websites with outstanding content. Layout, and functionalities using C#/ASP.NET and Angular.

- ✓ Designed, developed, and maintained multiple dynamic and browser compatible pages, reaching over 250,000 users, using HTML, CSS, and JavaScript frameworks such as React/Node and Python/ Django.
- ✓ Built a web application MVP for a dropship management platform with 75+ business customers

to create manage and monitor deliveries using Node, and Python. Ethers for integrating Ethereum.

- ✓ Developed 1 decentralized social media web application using React, CSS, Bootstrap and web3,js.
- ✓ Devised an Ethereum smart contracts and MVP that allowed over 3.9K developers to sell software licenses using 17 embeddable widgets.
- ✓ Involved in full life cycle of the project from requirements gathering, analyzing, designing Ul/data base using agile scrum methodology.

Phantom Network

Full Stack Engineer March 2019 - July 2022 (3 years 5 months)

- ✓ Managed team of 7+ members and monitored projects to ensure progress
- ✓ Increase revenue by 10% over the course of 2 years.
- ✓ Led design, and development of 30+ new features.
- ✓ Developed 3+ applications following Agile software methodologies using Next/TailwindCSS, Python/Django, and AWS.
- ✓ Collaborated with 2 different development cross-functional teams on 4 new projects designs and feature improvement.
- ✓ Delivered outstanding UX for 50,000+ customers, driving the usability, look, and feel of both mobile and ios app to achieve 300+ new 5-star ratings using React Native and Xcode.

Node Audio Ltd Full Stack Developer June 2018 - December 2018 (7 months)

Fleamint

Mid - Senior Full Stack Developer February 2015 - April 2017 (2 years 3 months)

- ✓ Designed and configured database and backend applications and programs, contributing to operations continuity and increasing efficiency by 14%.
- ✓ Worked on the improvement of data protection and security, increasing the security rate by 24% while creating new user information solutions.

✓ Launched 2 original e-commerce website and web applications, encompassing design, coding, testing, and maintenance with a team of 5 web developers.

✓ Coordinated with the engineering team of 35 to discuss user interface ideas and application.

Education

University of Toronto

Bachelor's degree, Computer Science